Guide to the Meyer Lissner Papers, 1903-1923 (inclusive), 1910-1920 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- AS - AV
  - Gabbert, J. R. - Oxnard 1911 -ed. & prepr. Daily Oxnard Courier
  - Galloway, J.D. - S.F. 1912civil engr.
  - Gamut Club - L.A.? s. F.W. Blanchard, pres.; st. L.E. Behymer, v.p.; st. G.M. Derby, sec.
  - Garbutt, Frank A. - L.A. 1920, 21
  - Garfield, James R. - Cleveland, Ohio 1919atty? son of Jas. A.
  - Garland, W.M. & Co. - L.A.? 1912, 17s. H.A. Helmy s. E.F. Cresby, s. Wm. M. Garland
  - Gates, Egbert J. - L.A. 1913, 17Calif. Assb.
  - Gates, George A. - Clarement 1907, 08pres. Pomona College
  - Gates, Lee C. - San Jose 1910, 12law dept. Tufle Ins. & Trust Co
  - Gayetti, A. (Miss) - S.F. 1911Calif Outlook
  - Geissler, E. A. - L.A. 1915Geo. J. Burkel Co. v.p.
  - Gelder, George - Oakland 1918Calif. Assb. (Hollywood)
  - Gerberding, E.O. - Hueneme, Cal. 1907, 18sec to Thomas R. Bard res. agt. Conn. Fire Ins. Co.
  - Gerecht, E. F. - L.A. 1912atty, *Hebrew Club
  - German Savings & Loan Soc. - S.F. 1916 *s. Geo. Tourny v.p. & mgr.
  - Gibbon, T.E. - L.A. 1911-13,19L.A. Herald? atty
  - Gibson, Hugh S - Dublin 1916, 1917, 18, 19, 20Dept. of State? Hoover & Food Cmm. American Minister to Poland
  - Gibson, Mary S. (Mrs. Frank A.) - L.A. 1912, 13, 16, 18, 19 & n.d.mother of Hugh Calif. Cmm. of Immigration & Housing cmmr.
  - Gilbert, E. J. - San Bernardino 1915 -cty. assessor
  - Gilbertson, H.S. - N.Y. 1915exec. sec. Nat'l Short Ballot Org.
  - Gillis, J. L. - Sacramento 1915State Librarian
  - Glenn Cty. Repub. Cent. Com. - Willows 1912s. John A. Apperson sec s. W. H. Sale county clerk
  - Globe Indemnity Co. - L.A. 1916s. Wm. R. Hellganz claim adjuster s. R.G. Hillman mgr. surety dept.
  - Goetz, E. P. - Indianapolis, Ind. 1910sec. to Senator A J Beveridge
  - Goldsmith, Arthur A. - Stanford U. 1916, 17L.A. 1918?atty, Vancouver, Wn. 1918
  - Goodman, Frank J. - N.Y. 1912Columbia U. faculty of polit sci
  - Goodwin, Willard L. - L.A. 1905sec. City Council Coms
  - Graham, S.C. - L.A. 1910, 11, 12chairman Good Govt. Org.
  - Grand Army of the Republic - L.A. (46th Nat'l Encampment) 1912st. Sidney A. Butler chairman
  - Grand Pacific Hotel - Chicago 1912s. E.A. Whipple, mgr.
  - Grant, F.F. - San Diego 1916 -atty. chairman Co. Progressive Party
  - Graupner, A.E. - S.F. 1919counsel Calif. Indus. Acc. Cmm.
  - Graves, M.O. - L. A. 1916atty candidate for Calif. Assb.
  - Good Government - L.A. 1909-11 & n.d.n.s. S.C. Graham chairman. Fund 1909 Mar. pres. Mar. 1909, Oct. 1910, 11st. Lucian J. Clarke. sec. Jul. 1909n.s Meyer Lissner, pres. Nov. 1909n.s. Marshall Stimson, pres. Dec. 1909st. Charles E. Bent, sec. Apr. 1910s. & st. Geo. B. Anderson, sec. Oct. 1910 - Nov. 1911
  - Good Govt. League - Stacy, Calif 1913s. C.R. Caudle, sec.
  - Great Northern Pacific Steamship Co. - L.A. 1916s. G.N. Koeppel agt.
  - Greenebaum Alfred - S.F. 11 1916, 17Calif. Non-Partisan League treas.; pres. Alaska Codfish Co.
  - Greene, B. D. Marx - Berkeley 1919atty
  - Greenhood, Ed. - Oakland 1908, 11-13, 15-17, 19, 20cousin of Lissners
  - Gregson, F.P. - L.A. 1910, 21Assoc. Jobbers of L.A. traffic mgr. & sec.
  - Grey, Elmer - L.A. 1913architect, (1)
  - Griffin, Franklin A. - Sacramento 1911, 12exec. sec.
  - Griffin, Maurice - Riverside 1908
  - Haggard, R.E. - S.F. 1919Calif Indus. Acc. Cmm.
  - Halfhill & Converse - L.A. 1915Henry S. Noyes
  - Hannan, John J. - Madison, Wisc. 1910 - 11, 12sec. to R. LaFolletle
  - Hamilton, John J. - L. A. 1912 - 13, 15, 19sec. L.A. Charter Revision Com. sec. L.A. Bd. of Freeholders, pres. Calif. Acreage Investment Co; Greater L.A. Realty Co., L.A. Co. Bd. of Supervisors supv. & chairman
  - Handley, Loren A. - L.A. 1911, 12City Clerk, prof. of philosophy Ocadental College
  - Hamilton & Goodman - L.A. 1915s. Harry B. Goodman
  - Hanford, [A.I.] - San Bernardino 1907?mayor
  - Hansen, A.C. - L.A. 1912Inspector of Public Works
  - [Hapgood], Norman - N.Y. 1908-10Collier's editorial staff
  - Hardy, Campbell - 1906, 10, 16contracts for publishing houses
  - Hargrove, Robert L, - Madera 1912chairman. Madera Co. Repub Cent. Com.
  - Harper, A.C. - L.A. 1908mayor chairman pro-tem Permanent Org. of Municipal Waterways Assoc.
  - Harriman, T.E. - L.A. 1917, (1)
  - *Harris, H. H. - L.A. 1912, 15, 17, 18, 19sec. City Charter Conf. sec. City Club of L.A.,? A.F.C. Amer. Exped. Forces
  - Hart, Alfred Bashneil - Cambridge, Mass. 1911, 12prof. of govt. Harvard
  - Hart, Edwin G. L.A. 1915
  - Hart, John W. - L.A. 1919atty personal, (1)
  - Haskell, Sidney M. - L.A. 1908, 13mgr. L.D. Powell Co. chairman Campaign Com. L-R. Repub Lg.
  - Hatton, A.R. - Cleveland, Ohio 1912Western Reserve Univ. Poli Sci Dept
  - Havenner, Franck R. - 1914, 15, 20, 21Calif legis. reporter for Calif.; sec. ? to Hiram Johnson
  - Hawley, J O. - L.A. 1908, 10, 11pension atty, sec. H.PKP - Impot. Lge? (Highland Pk Protective & Improvement League) & Good Govt. to Hawley verse Jul. 7, 1911
  - Hayes, E.A. - Wn. D.C. 1907(1)? U.S. Hse of Representatives, (1)
  - Hayes, J.O. - S.F. 1918
  - Hayward, W. A. - Des Moines, Iowa 1912Iowa Sec. of St.
  - Hayward, William - Chicago 1912 -sec. Repub. Nat'l. Com.
  - Haynard Hotel - L.A. 1915, 20s. H.C. Fryman, prep.? B. F. Klein
  - Hebrew Benevolent Soc. - L.A. 1915 -sec. s. Henry L. Klein
  - Heard, Dwight B. - Phoenix, Ariz. 1912, 13, 16pres. Arizona Republican
  - Hebrew Club -? L.A. 1912resolution re: Abe Ruef s. M. Stutz, pres. s. John I. Mess, sec.
  - Hecht, S. - L.A. 1910rabbi of Congregation B'Nai B'rith
  - Hays, Will H. - N.Y. Indianapolis, Ind. 1918-21chairman Repub. Nat'l Com. U.S. Postmaster General
  - Haynes, John Randolph - L.A. 1908, 09, 11, 14, 16, 17-20, 21Direct Legislation Lg.
  - Henderson, Frank G. - L.A. 1910-12, 17sec. City Club of L.A. affl. reporter Hau of Records
  - Henderson, Thomas L. - (Nevada) 1904civil & mining engr.
  - Heney, Ben - Tucson, Ariz. 190810, 12 -? recorder, Pima County, pres. & mgr. Ben Heney
  - Heney for Governor League - S.F. 1918s. Frank V. Cornish, sec.
  - Herald News Co. - El paso, Tex. 1908
  - Herriott, Paul - Sacramento 1917?Calif. St. Bd. of Control sec. to Sen. H.W. Johnson partner
  - Heney, Francis J. - S.F. 1907-08, 09, 10 11-14atty Charles W. Cobb Lincoln-Roosevelt Repub. Lg.
  - Hewitt, Leslie R. - L.A. 1908, 10-13spec. counsel Bur. Harbor Cmmrs Bd. Pub Util., City Atty
  - Hill, A. J. - L.A. 1915County Counsel
  - Hillcrest Country Club - L.A. 1920, 21
  - Hilles, Charles D. - N.Y. 1912chairman. Rep. Nat'l Com.
  - Hinshaw, W.E. - Long Beach, Cal. 1908-11, 16Sec. Wilmington Dock Co sec. Joint Senatorial & Assb. Delegation, Calif. Assb., sec L.A. Co. Deleg, L. A. Co. Bd. of Supervisors
  - Hichborn, Franklin - Santa Clara 1910-11, 15newspaperman, corres. sec. Calif Non-Partisan League
  - Hoak, E. K. - L.A. 1915mgr. Pacific Coast Dept. Doubleday Page & Co.
  - Hocking, T. C. - Modesto, Cal. 1912pres. Herald Publishing Co.
  - Hodghead, Beverly L. - S. F. 1907, 11atty, Berkeley mayor; pres. League of Calif. Municipalities
  - Hodgin, E. Stanton - L.A. 1915, 19minister First unitarian Church
  - Holder, Charles F. - Pasadena Avalon, Cal. 1912, 13
  - Holland, Henry - Portland, Me. 1916, 17, 19 -mgr. Maine branch Nat'l Workmen's Compensation Service Bureau, dist. mgr. Federal Mut. Liab. Ins. Co.
  - Home Ins. Co. - N.Y. L.A. 1911s. Charles Quitzow, spec. agt.; s. Emanuel H.A. Corred v.p.
  - Home Life Ins. Co. - N.Y. 1907s. George E. Ide, pres.
  - Home Rule in Taxation (So. Calif. League for) - L.A. 1912s. Bernard Hartley sec. st. Clarence E. Todd (S.F.) sec. & campaign mgr
  - Home Security Loan Soc - Caleland 1906s. C.P. Hoag, sec.
  - Hooker, E.H. - N.Y. 1912treas. Progressive Nat'l Com.
  - Hooker, George E. - Chicago 1911, 12civic sec. City Cl. of Chicago
  - Hooker, Katherine - S. F. 1911-13, 15
  - Hopkins, Edward W. - L.A. 1907, 12County Assessor
  - House & Garden - Philadelphia 1907s. E.L.D. Reach Circulation
  - Houser, Frederick W. - Sacramento 1905, 09, 10Calif Assb., L.A. Superior Ct
  - Houser, F.W., Campaign Com. - L.A. 1912s. Robert Mitchell, chairman.
  - Houser, Walter L. - Wn. D.C. 1911chairman Progressive Repub. Campaign
  - Howard, Clifford - L.A. 1912sec. L. A. Soc. of Social Hygiene
  - Howard, Ray - L.A. 1908, 10, 11, 15, 16, 18-20 & n.d.atty
  - Howat, Marshall, Macmillan & Crow - Salt Lake City 1921s. Ben Stewart Crew
  - Howe, Edgar F. - El Centro 1912, 17ed. & mgr. Imperial Valley Press; The Zanjero (Supervisor of Canals) editor
  - Hoxie, George L. - N.Y. 1911electrical engr.
  - Habbard, Carson B - L.A. 1920atty for Nat'l Adjusting Assoc.
  - Hubbell Publishing Co. - N.Y. 1919s. George Heller, sec.
  - Hull, Morton Demsen - Chicago 1908atty
  - Hull, Warren - Seattle, Wn. 1920, 21
  - Humboldt County Repub. Cent. Com. - Eureka 1912s. George W. Cousins, co. clerk; s. Fred M. Kay, sec.
  - Humphreys, John H. - London, England 1912sec. Proportional Representation Soc.
  - Hunsaker, William J. - L.A. 1907, 08, 11, 12, 20atty
  - Hunt, Myron - L.A. 1912, 19architect A.C. Arnoldy
  - Hunt & Burns - L.A. 1912, 13architects s. Summer Hunt
  - Hunter, J.M. - L.A. 1911, 12mgr. Provident Mat Bldg. & Loan Assn
  - Huntington, H.E. - L.A. L.Y. 1911(2)
  - Hurlbut, J.L. - Sanata Barbara 1912 -chairman. Sta. Barb. Repub. Cent. Com. pres. Sta. Barb. Paring & Grading Co.
  - Hutchins, D. S. - S. F. Crescent City 1910, 20
  - Hutton, Frank S. - L.A. 1910, 12, 17-20atty, sec. Roosevelt Pregr. Repub. League, chairman Memorial Com. L.A. Bar Assoc.? Calif. Adj. Gen. Office, Santa Monica
  - Hutton, George H. - L.A. 1911, 16atty judge Superior Ct.
  - Imperial Co Repub. Cent. Com. - El Centro 1912s. Phil D. Swing chairman
  - Industrial Relations, Com. on - N.Y. 1912Edward T. Devine chairman exec. com.
  - Ingersoll, Luther A. - L.A.?
  - Internal Rev. Serv. - Indianapolis, S.F. 1919Ind. 1917s. Peter J. Kruger, collector; L.A. 1920s. C. Dewitt, deputy collector
  - Inyo Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - Independence, Cal. 1912s. George R. Shuey [Scituate?], Mass
  - Irwin, Will - N.Y. 1912, 19?Progressive Nat'l Com.
  - Ickes, Harold L. - Chicago 1915, 16, 17, 19, 20Progressive Natl Com. man fr. Ill.; chairman Progressive atty Pty of Ill.; Progr. Repub. Prelim Mtg, temp. sec.
  - Idaho Dept. of State - Boise, Idaho 1913s. W.L. Gifford, Sec. of St.
  - Jackman, S. J. - Santa Ana 1915-16chairman Orange Co. Repub. Cent. Com., (1912)
  - Jackson, J.E. - L.A. 1913see. to Elmer Grey
  - Jacobs, Isidor - S.F. 1909-12pres. Calif Canneries Co., S.F. Good Govt. chairman campaign
  - James & Ryan - Gooding, Idaho 1919s. M.F. Ryan atty
  - James, William P. - L.A. 1917 -Justice Dist. Court of Appeal (2nd dist.)
  - Jeffries, W.P., Co. - L.A. 1919, 20engravers *s. W.P. Jeffries, pres.; s. F.J. Wooley, Jr., v.p.
  - Jeffrey, J.W. - Sacramento 1911.St. (Cal.) Cmmr. of Horticulture
  - Jess, Stoddard - L.A. 1910-12, 15, 16, 18pres. & v.p. 1st Nat'l Bank of L.A. pres. L.A. Clearing House Assn. Municipal Conf. of 1913, pres.
  - Jewish Charities of L.A. (Com. on Fed. of) - L.A, 1911, 12s. Ben R. Meyer, D.W. Edelman, Henry W. Laing, Louis M. Cole, L. Beluenolt, John Kahn, Louis S. Nordlinger; s. Esther Shu, asst. sec.
  - Jewish Charities of L.A. (Fed. of) - L.A. 1915, 16, 19 n.d.same as above s. George Mosbacher, pres., s. Henry L. Klein, sec., Josephine Rosenberg, s. of L.A.
  - Jewish Colonial Trust & Nat'l Fund Com. - L.A. 1906s. H. Fram, sec.
  - Jewish Community Com. of L.A. - L.A. 1919s. Louis S. Nordlinger, sec. pre tem.
  - Johnson, Wm Templeton - San Diego 1915architect
  - Johnstone, Herbert W. - Highland, Cal. 1908, 11, 12pres. 1st Nat'l Bank of Highland; deputy State Treasurer
  - Jones, B.R. - L.A. 1911
  - Jones, C. Colcock - L.A. 1914consulting mining engr. re: Panama Canal
  - Johnson, George H. - San Bernardino 1916-20atty Calif. Assb.,? Indus. Acc. Cmm., U.S. Army 2nd Lt.
  - Johnson, Hiram W. - S.F. Visalia, Cal. 1910 - 1918, 1920, 21atty, Gov. 1911-17U. S. Senator 1917-see also Alex. McCabe, Martin Madsen; H.W. Jr., (19 folders)
  - Johnson, Hiram W., Jr. - S.F. 1910 - 21atty sometimes s. Jack
  - Johnson for Senator Club - L.A. 1916 - 18, 22s. Mary E. Smith, sec.
  - Johnston, James A. - Sacramento 1912-14, 17, 21, n.d.chairman. Cal. St. Bd. of Control warden St. Prison at Folsom warden, San Quentin Prison
  - Johnstone, W. A. - San Dumas 1907, 08, 11, 12, 15, 16-20Pres. Bank of San Dumas First Nat'l Bk of S. Dumas memb exec. com. L. A. Co. Cent. Com. L-R Repub. Lg., Pres. State Water Cmm
  - Jones, S. P. - Minneapolis, Minn. 1911, 12Sec. Voters League
  - * Jones, William Carey - Berkeley 1908, 12, 15, 19, 20U.C.-Dept. of Jurisprudence chairman. Admin. Bd. U.C.
  - * Jordan, David Starr - Stanford 1907, 11, 12Pres. Stanford U. chief director, World Peace Foundation
  - * Jordan, Frank C. - Sacramento 1911, 12, 19Cal. Sec. of State J.M. Cremin, statistician
  - Juillard, Louis W. - Santa Rosa 1910, 11Calif. Assb.
  - Justice, O. M. - L.A. 1910M.D., (1)
  - * Jewish Agricultural Experiment Station (at Haifa, Palestine) - N.Y. 19s. Louis Marshall, Julian W. Mack, [J W.] Magnes
  - * Johnson, Mrs. Hiram W. - Wn., D. C. 1917, (1)
  - Kahn, Julius - Wn. D.C. 1910U.S. Congressman (Cal.)
  - Kawakaml, K.K. - S.F. 1915, 20mgr. Pacific Press author
  - Keating, J. Edward - San Diego 1919, 20atty, justice of the peace
  - Keesling, Francis V. - S.F. 1911, 19atty ltrs. not important, (2)
  - Kellogg, D.D. - Pasadena 1911, 12Pasadena City Auditor s. J.W.Prinz, deputy
  - Kellogg, Francis B. - L.A. 1908, 10-14, 19M.D.
  - Kellogg, Paul U. - N. Y. 13, 1915, 19, 20editor, The Survey
  - Kellor, Frances A. - N. Y. 1913Chf. of Service - Progressive Service Bd., Progr. Nat'l Committee
  - Kendall, B.O. Co. - Pasadena, 1915s. W. E. Olivet
  - Kennedy, Arthur W. - L.A. 1920, 21grand regent, Grand Council of the Boya Arcanum
  - Kennedy, Herbert D. - L.A. 1907Mayor's clerk & sec. to Mayor A.C. Harper
  - Kent for Senator - S.F. 1920st. Preston L. Higgins
  - Keppel, Hark - L.A. 1911, 12Supt. of Schools, L.A. County
  - Kern, W.B. - Norwalk, Cal. 1914, 17Med. Supt. Norwalk State Hospital
  - Kern Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - Bakers field 1912Barclay McCowan, chrmn
  - Keyes, C.G. - L.A. 1908L.A. County Clerk
  - Kiefer, Daniel - Cincinnati, O. 1911not signed. Cmm. Joseph Fels Fund of Am
  - * King, Lyman M. - Redlands 1910, 11chrmn San Bernardino Co. Repub. Co. Central C. editor Redlands Daily Facts
  - King, Grace B. - Long Beach 1915pres. Women's City Club of Long Beach
  - Kings Co. Repub Cent. Com. - Hanford, Cal, s. E.R. Houston, sec.
  - Kingsbury, W.S. - Sacramento 1911California Surveyor Gen.
  - Kingsley, Bruce Gorden - L.A. 1911? Music Travelognes musician
  - Kinney, H.H. - Pomena 1910-13pres. Pomona Times Publishing
  - * Kent, William - Kentfield, Marin Co. 1908, 10-13U.S. House of Re John E. Webb, see.
  - Klauber Wangenheim Co. - L.A. 1915s. E.E. Klauber
  - Klenert, Abram - Paterson, N. J. 1919atty
  - Kline, Eugene F. L.A. 1915, 17s. Gene former partner of Lewinsohn
  - Kline, Sheda (Mrs. E.F.) - L.A. 1921
  - Klink, Bean Co. - L.A. 1912s. C.S. Black
  - Klokke, Carl C. - L.A. 1915, 16, 19, 20res. agt. German Alliance Ins. Ass & American Alliance
  - Klokke Investment Co. - L.A. 1916, 21s. Ernst A. Klekke, treas., Korl C. Klekke
  - Knight, George A. - S.F. 1911Repub. Natl Com.
  - Knowles, Willes B. - San Quentin 1918, 1919prisoner
  - ?Knox, Frank - Mieh. & Camp Dix, N.S. (Manehester, N.H.) 1912, 17pres. & ed. Union-Leader Publishing Co
  - * Koebig, A.H. - L.A. 1917engineer, (1)
  - Koenig, Samuel S. - N.Y. 1920pres. Repub. Co. Com.
  - Koepfll, S.O. - L.A. 1908, 10, 13, 14, 19Bishop & Co.
  - Koiner, C. Wellington - Pasadena 1910, 11engineer, mgr., Pasadena Municipal Lighting Dept.
  - Krehbiel, Edward - Stanford 1916, 18-20Dept. of Head., Stanford University; Pacific Gast rep. of Survey
  - Kuhl, Max - S.F. 1911, 18atty
  - Kunze, C.E. - Bishop, Cal. 1911ed. Owens Valley Heralal
  - Kihm, M. - N.Y. 1913sec. to [G.W.] Perkins
  - Kilner, W.H. - L.A. 1913sec. to Arthur Letts
  - Labor, U.S. Dept. of (Bureau of Labor Statistics) - Wn. D.C. 1919st. Royal Meeker, cmmt.
  - Lake Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - Lakeport 1912s. Fred A. Greene, sec.
  - Lakes - to-the-Gulf Deep Waterway Assoc. - St. Louis (Mo.?) 1912s. William K. Karanaugh, pres.
  - Lamb, W.A. - ? Sacramento 1911Calif. Assb. chrmn. com. on Retrenchment Reform
  - Lane, Franklin K. - Wn. D.C. 1913, 17, 18Sec. of Interor
  - Lang, Ellen F. - L.A. 1913
  - Lawler, Oscar - L.A. 1921atty
  - League of Justice - L.A. 1911s. A. lan I. Warren, sec.
  - Langdon, William H. - Modesto, 1911,S.F. 1919 -justice dist. ct. of appeals
  - Langley, John W. - Louisville, Ky. 1911chairman. Kentacky Repub. St. Campaign Com.
  - Langmuir, Charles H. - L.A. 1913, 15, 17, 18, 19N.Y. Life Ins. Co. L.A. agd campaign dit. Natl Food - Pledge Campaign of the U.S. Food Admin pres. L.A. Municipal League
  - Lapp, John A. - Indianapolis, Ind. 1912 -legis. ref. lib. Indiana St. Lib
  - Lassen Co. Clerk (Repub. Co. Cent. Com.) - Susanville 1912s. George E. Bassett, co. clk.
  - Lathrop, Dorothy M. - (Mrs. John) Berkeley 1917
  - Lathrop, John E. N.Y. 1915, 17
    - American City Bureau, dit. Dept. of Exhibits
  - Laukota, Garriott Co., Inc. - L.A. 1915s. Fred A. Brown, sec. Lawyer
  - Lawlor, William P. - S.F. 1920assoc. justice Supreme Ct. of Calif.
  - Lawyers Co-op Publishing Co. - Rochester, N.Y. 1920s. Metle G. Drale
  - La Follette, Robert M. - Wn. D.C. 1909, 10, 11U.S. Senator, Wisconsin; John J. Hauman = sec. (or Hannan)
  - League for Preservation of Amer. Independence - Wn. D.C. 1919s. James E. Clark, mgr. natl HQ; s. Fred C. Spaulding, mgr, Frank S. Hutton L.A. temp. se.
  - League to Protect the Initiative - L.A. 1920s. Bertha L. Cable, sec. lawyer
  - Lee, Bradner W. - L.A. 1913
  - Levinson & Hoffman - Chicago 1920s. Harry C. Levinson and Lea W. Hoff
  - Lewis, E. David - Cedar Rapids, Iowa 1911Cousin ofLessner
  - Lincoln Memorial University - Cumberland Gap, Tenn. 1911s. W.S. Gilbert.
  - Lincoln - Roosevelt Repub LG. - L.A. Co. Cent. Com. 1908,10s. Kemper B. Camp bell, sec.
  - Lippincott, J.B. - L.A. 1911, 12,13 15, 18asst. chief engr. L.A. Aqueduct consulting hydraulic engr.
  - Lippincott, Josephine (Mrs. J. B.) - n.d.,n.p.
  - Locomobile Co. of America, - L.A. 1913,16s. J. Murray Page res. mgr. s. H. M. Cart, branch supt.
  - Loewenthal, Max - L.A. 1919atty, (1)
  - Long, Percy V. - S.F. 1915city atty.
  - Long Beach, Cal. Daily Telegram - Long Beach 1913s. Geo. W. MacDonnell ad mgr.
  - Long Beach, Women's City Club of - Long Beach 1915s. Grace, B. King, pres
  - League of Calif. Municipalities - S.F. 1911s. W. J. Looke asst. sec
  - League of Justice - L.A. 1911s. A. I. Warren, sec.
  - League to Enforce Peace - N.Y. 1918, 19st. Wm. H. Taft et al, pres. st. Chas. C. Moore et al, chairman. dist. Com. Calif. Nev. Ariz. Benj. Ide Wheeler, Calif St. chairman
  - Lee, E. M. - Jeffersonville, Indianapolis, Ind. 1914, 15, 16?Indiana Reformed Indiana Progr. State Com.?
  - Leeds, Walter R. - Sacramento 1907, 08Calif. Assb. L.A. atty
  - Leightop, E.E. - L.A. 1912, 1907, [08?]sec. Peoples Charter Conf.
  - Lelande, Harry J. - L.A. 1921sec. Meorpark Oil Co.
  - Lemon, Will F. - San Bernardino 1910chairman & st. rep. - St. Legis. Bd. Order of Railway Conductors
  - Letts, Arthur - (N.Y.) L.A. 1910, 11, 13, 19sec. W. H. B. Kilner
  - Levy, S. Leonard - Pittsburgh, Pa. 1910, 12, 13, 15, 16relig, polit, pers. rabbi Rodeph Shalons Congregation? House of the Seven Gables
  - Lewy, Raphael - N.Y. 1918M.D. chf med. examiner N.Y. Labor Dept.
  - Lewinsohn, Joseph L. - L.A. 1915, 17 - 21see also Corresp. Out
  - Lickley, Ernest J. - L.A. 1911sap lawyer, partner of Lissner, anti. Lg of Nations. Compulsory Ed. & Evening Schools Sch. D L.A.C
  - Lincoln, Robert T. - Chicago 1909son of Abraham, (1)
  - Lincoln - Roosevelt Colored Repub. Lg. of So. Cal. - L.A. 1910s. Isider D. Blair, chairman
  - Lind, H.B. - Reno, Nev. 1912chairman. Nevada Progr. St. Cent. Com.
  - Lindley, Curtis H. - S.F. 1912lawyer
  - Lindsey, Ben B. - Denver, Colo 1912judge Juvenile Court
  - Linnard, D.M. - Pasadena 1911, 18mgr. Maryland Hotel California Chain - Fairmont (S.F.), pro. So. Cal. Publicity Bd.
  - Lissner, Aline 1919daughter b. [? 1912, Apr.]
  - Lissner, Bert or Bertheld - 1912, 17, 18, 24, n.d.brother
  - Lissner, Elsa (Mrs. Bert) - S.F. 1920, 21
  - [Lissner], Elsie n.d.n.p. -? same as above, signs, Sister Elsie to Doody
  - Lissner, Ermine - Greenhood (Mrs. Meyer) - 1913, 16, 18, 19, 21, n.d.
  - Lissner, Jay - Menle Pk. 1919son
  - Lissner, Louis M. - 1913, 15-17, 18, 19 21, n.d.son & jr. law partner see also Corresp. Out
  - Lissner, William - S.F. 1911cousin
  - Lissner, Henry H. - L.A. 1910, 13, 16, 17, 18, 20brother M.D.
  - Lockwood, [N. or M.] W. - Riverside 1915 17?National League for the Protection of the Family
  - Locomobile Co of America - L.A. 1913, 16s. S. Murray Page res. mgr. s. H.M. Cain branch supt.
  - Loeb, Albert I. - S.F. 1910, 12, 13, 16, 20atty
  - Loeb, Joseph P. - L.A. 1919, 20atty Loeb, Walker & Loeb
  - Loewenthal, Max - L.A. 1910, 13, 15, 19,* 20, 21atty & distrib successful American Products
  - Long, Percy V. - S.F. 1915City Atty pres. Calif. Conf. on City Planning 1915, 16
  - Long Beach Daily Telegram - Long Beach 1913s. Geo. W. Mac Donnell ad. mg
  - Long Beach Women's City Club - Long Beach 1915s. Grace B. King, pres.
  - Loose, C.E. - Provo, Utah [1911]chrmn, Utah State Republican, (1 tel.)
  - Louis, E.J. - L.A. 1910, 11, 17Cmdr. U.S.N., Naval attaché to Calif. Gov.; agt. - Fidelity & Casualty Co. of N.Y. s. Monnie, mgr. Louis Underwriters Agency
  - Loveland, Harrey D. - S.F. 1910, 11cmmr Calif. R R Cmm.
  - Lowell, A. Lawrence - Cambridge, Mass. 1919?Harvard U. pres. off.
  - Los Angeles Architectural Club - L.A. 1912s Norman D. Bishop exhib. mgr
  - L.A. Chamber of Commerce - L.A. 1908, 11-12, 13, 15, 16, 18, 20, 21s. & st. Frank Wiggins, sec.; st. H.B. Gurley, asst. sec.; s. James Slanson, pres.; s. T.G. Williams for Clarence H. Matson, mgr. Trade Extension Cmm
  - L.A. Charter Revision Cmm. - L.A. 1912s. John J. Hamilton
  - L.A. City Assessor - L.A. 1916ptd. Walter Mallard
  - L.A. City Atty - L.A. 1910s.* John W. Shenk
  - L.A. City Clerk - 1917St. Charles L. Wilde
  - L.A. City Teachers' Club - 1919s. Burney Porter, cor. sec.
  - L.A. City Council - L.A. 1915s. W.C. Lewis, sec.
  - L.A. Dept., College of Medicine, U. of C. - 1910s. George H. Kiess, sec. of fac.
  - L.A. Education Bo. - 1915s. Wm. A. Sheldon, see.
  - L.A. Examiner - 1908, 11, 18, 20s. W. P. Anderson, mg. editor F.W. Braun mg. ed, s. [ M. F. Hansen] genl. mgr., s. W. H. Price mgr Credits & Collections
  - L.A. Freeholders Bd:- 1912s. John J. Hamilton, sec.
  - L.A. Freeholders Franchise Com. 1912, n.d.ptd. F. W. Braun minority Lewis R. Works chrmn
  - L.A. Freeholders Law Com. 1912ptd. Charles Wellborn, chrmn
  - L.A. Harbor Cmmrs - 1913, 17s. [ F. D. Woodman] pres. t. Clarence H. Matson 1917see. & traffic mgr.; s. Christopher M. Gordon pres. 1917Lissner a member
  - L.A. Health Dept., Bur of Housing Cmm, - 1915, 26s. John E. Kienle exec. sec.; s. Dana W. Bartlett, chrmn. spec. com. on indus. housing s. F.D. [Swiger], exec. sec.
  - L.A. Herald - 1911s. H. S. Sharpless, bus mgr.
  - L.A. Highschool - 1911s. C.E. Goyette, student body pres.
  - L.A. Ice & Cold Storage Co. - 1911s. J. G. McKinney, mgr.
  - L.A. Municipal League. 1914, 16, 18, 19, n.d. &Elbert Wing, pres.; & H.S. Ryerson, sec.; s. Seward C. Simons, sec.
  - Municipal League of s. Charles H. Langmuir, pres.; s. Authony Pratt (by E. Witbey) sec.
  - L.A. Municipal League - Recall Campaign Com. n.d.? &S.C. Graham, chrmn, & E.O. Edgerton, sec.
  - L. A. Mystic Shrine - L.A. 1912s.* Motley H. Flunt, chrmn exec. com.
  - L.A. Park Dept. - 1912, 14, 15s. C.T. Herbert, see., Bd. Pk. Cmmrs. s.*. B. Lippincott, Park Cmmt; s. F. Shearet, supt.